{
    "irrelevant": [
        {
            "model_response": "mpox",
            "needle": "The most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO is Clade I mpox.",
            "context_length": 0,
            "depth_percent": 0.0,
            "question": "What is the disease associated with the most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO?",
            "frequency": 5,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "mpox",
            "needle": "The most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO is Clade I mpox.",
            "context_length": 0,
            "depth_percent": 100.0,
            "question": "What is the disease associated with the most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO?",
            "frequency": 5,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "mpox",
            "needle": "The most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO is Clade I mpox.",
            "context_length": 0,
            "depth_percent": 25.0,
            "question": "What is the disease associated with the most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO?",
            "frequency": 5,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "mpox",
            "needle": "The most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO is Clade I mpox.",
            "context_length": 0,
            "depth_percent": 50.0,
            "question": "What is the disease associated with the most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO?",
            "frequency": 5,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "mpox",
            "needle": "The most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO is Clade I mpox.",
            "context_length": 0,
            "depth_percent": 75.0,
            "question": "What is the disease associated with the most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO?",
            "frequency": 5,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "COVID-19",
            "needle": "The most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO is Clade I mpox.",
            "context_length": 1250,
            "depth_percent": 0.0,
            "question": "What is the disease associated with the most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO?",
            "frequency": 14,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Clade I mpox",
            "needle": "The most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO is Clade I mpox.",
            "context_length": 1250,
            "depth_percent": 100.0,
            "question": "What is the disease associated with the most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO?",
            "frequency": 5,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "COVID-19",
            "needle": "The most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO is Clade I mpox.",
            "context_length": 1250,
            "depth_percent": 25.0,
            "question": "What is the disease associated with the most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO?",
            "frequency": 14,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "COVID-19",
            "needle": "The most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO is Clade I mpox.",
            "context_length": 1250,
            "depth_percent": 50.0,
            "question": "What is the disease associated with the most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO?",
            "frequency": 14,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "COVID-19",
            "needle": "The most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO is Clade I mpox.",
            "context_length": 1250,
            "depth_percent": 75.0,
            "question": "What is the disease associated with the most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO?",
            "frequency": 14,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "COVID-19",
            "needle": "The most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO is Clade I mpox.",
            "context_length": 2500,
            "depth_percent": 0.0,
            "question": "What is the disease associated with the most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO?",
            "frequency": 14,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Clade I mpox",
            "needle": "The most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO is Clade I mpox.",
            "context_length": 2500,
            "depth_percent": 100.0,
            "question": "What is the disease associated with the most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO?",
            "frequency": 5,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "COVID-19",
            "needle": "The most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO is Clade I mpox.",
            "context_length": 2500,
            "depth_percent": 25.0,
            "question": "What is the disease associated with the most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO?",
            "frequency": 14,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "COVID-19",
            "needle": "The most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO is Clade I mpox.",
            "context_length": 2500,
            "depth_percent": 50.0,
            "question": "What is the disease associated with the most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO?",
            "frequency": 14,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "COVID-19",
            "needle": "The most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO is Clade I mpox.",
            "context_length": 2500,
            "depth_percent": 75.0,
            "question": "What is the disease associated with the most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO?",
            "frequency": 14,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "COVID-19",
            "needle": "The most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO is Clade I mpox.",
            "context_length": 3750,
            "depth_percent": 0.0,
            "question": "What is the disease associated with the most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO?",
            "frequency": 14,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Clade I mpox",
            "needle": "The most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO is Clade I mpox.",
            "context_length": 3750,
            "depth_percent": 100.0,
            "question": "What is the disease associated with the most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO?",
            "frequency": 5,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "COVID-19",
            "needle": "The most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO is Clade I mpox.",
            "context_length": 3750,
            "depth_percent": 25.0,
            "question": "What is the disease associated with the most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO?",
            "frequency": 14,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "COVID-19",
            "needle": "The most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO is Clade I mpox.",
            "context_length": 3750,
            "depth_percent": 50.0,
            "question": "What is the disease associated with the most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO?",
            "frequency": 14,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Clade I mpox",
            "needle": "The most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO is Clade I mpox.",
            "context_length": 3750,
            "depth_percent": 75.0,
            "question": "What is the disease associated with the most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO?",
            "frequency": 5,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "COVID-19",
            "needle": "The most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO is Clade I mpox.",
            "context_length": 5000,
            "depth_percent": 0.0,
            "question": "What is the disease associated with the most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO?",
            "frequency": 14,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Clade I mpox",
            "needle": "The most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO is Clade I mpox.",
            "context_length": 5000,
            "depth_percent": 100.0,
            "question": "What is the disease associated with the most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO?",
            "frequency": 5,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "COVID-19",
            "needle": "The most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO is Clade I mpox.",
            "context_length": 5000,
            "depth_percent": 25.0,
            "question": "What is the disease associated with the most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO?",
            "frequency": 14,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "COVID-19",
            "needle": "The most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO is Clade I mpox.",
            "context_length": 5000,
            "depth_percent": 50.0,
            "question": "What is the disease associated with the most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO?",
            "frequency": 14,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Mpox",
            "needle": "The most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO is Clade I mpox.",
            "context_length": 5000,
            "depth_percent": 75.0,
            "question": "What is the disease associated with the most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO?",
            "frequency": 1,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        }
    ],
    "irrelevant_misleading": [
        {
            "model_response": "mpox",
            "needle": "The most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO is Clade I mpox.",
            "context_length": 0,
            "depth_percent": 0.0,
            "question": "What is the disease associated with the most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO?",
            "frequency": 5,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "mpox",
            "needle": "The most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO is Clade I mpox.",
            "context_length": 0,
            "depth_percent": 100.0,
            "question": "What is the disease associated with the most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO?",
            "frequency": 5,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "mpox",
            "needle": "The most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO is Clade I mpox.",
            "context_length": 0,
            "depth_percent": 25.0,
            "question": "What is the disease associated with the most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO?",
            "frequency": 5,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "mpox",
            "needle": "The most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO is Clade I mpox.",
            "context_length": 0,
            "depth_percent": 50.0,
            "question": "What is the disease associated with the most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO?",
            "frequency": 5,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "mpox",
            "needle": "The most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO is Clade I mpox.",
            "context_length": 0,
            "depth_percent": 75.0,
            "question": "What is the disease associated with the most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO?",
            "frequency": 5,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "COVID-19",
            "needle": "The most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO is Clade I mpox.",
            "context_length": 1250,
            "depth_percent": 0.0,
            "question": "What is the disease associated with the most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO?",
            "frequency": 6,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Clade I mpox",
            "needle": "The most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO is Clade I mpox.",
            "context_length": 1250,
            "depth_percent": 100.0,
            "question": "What is the disease associated with the most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO?",
            "frequency": 8,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "COVID-19",
            "needle": "The most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO is Clade I mpox.",
            "context_length": 1250,
            "depth_percent": 25.0,
            "question": "What is the disease associated with the most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO?",
            "frequency": 6,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "COVID-19",
            "needle": "The most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO is Clade I mpox.",
            "context_length": 1250,
            "depth_percent": 50.0,
            "question": "What is the disease associated with the most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO?",
            "frequency": 6,
            "hallucination_type": "Irrelevant Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "COVID-19",
            "needle": "The most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO is Clade I mpox.",
            "context_length": 1250,
            "depth_percent": 75.0,
            "question": "What is the disease associated with the most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO?",
            "frequency": 6,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "COVID-19",
            "needle": "The most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO is Clade I mpox.",
            "context_length": 2500,
            "depth_percent": 0.0,
            "question": "What is the disease associated with the most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO?",
            "frequency": 6,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Clade I mpox",
            "needle": "The most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO is Clade I mpox.",
            "context_length": 2500,
            "depth_percent": 100.0,
            "question": "What is the disease associated with the most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO?",
            "frequency": 8,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "COVID-19",
            "needle": "The most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO is Clade I mpox.",
            "context_length": 2500,
            "depth_percent": 25.0,
            "question": "What is the disease associated with the most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO?",
            "frequency": 6,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Clade I mpox",
            "needle": "The most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO is Clade I mpox.",
            "context_length": 2500,
            "depth_percent": 50.0,
            "question": "What is the disease associated with the most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO?",
            "frequency": 8,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Clade I mpox, the most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by the World Health Organization (WHO) is Clade I mpox.",
            "needle": "The most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO is Clade I mpox.",
            "context_length": 2500,
            "depth_percent": 75.0,
            "question": "What is the disease associated with the most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO?",
            "frequency": 1,
            "hallucination_type": "Excess Incorrect Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Clade I mpox",
            "needle": "The most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO is Clade I mpox.",
            "context_length": 3750,
            "depth_percent": 0.0,
            "question": "What is the disease associated with the most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO?",
            "frequency": 8,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Clade I mpox",
            "needle": "The most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO is Clade I mpox.",
            "context_length": 3750,
            "depth_percent": 100.0,
            "question": "What is the disease associated with the most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO?",
            "frequency": 8,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Clade II mpox",
            "needle": "The most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO is Clade I mpox.",
            "context_length": 3750,
            "depth_percent": 25.0,
            "question": "What is the disease associated with the most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO?",
            "frequency": 1,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Clade I mpox",
            "needle": "The most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO is Clade I mpox.",
            "context_length": 3750,
            "depth_percent": 50.0,
            "question": "What is the disease associated with the most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO?",
            "frequency": 8,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Clade I mpox",
            "needle": "The most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO is Clade I mpox.",
            "context_length": 3750,
            "depth_percent": 75.0,
            "question": "What is the disease associated with the most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO?",
            "frequency": 8,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Clade X, it is a fictional outbreak.",
            "needle": "The most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO is Clade I mpox.",
            "context_length": 5000,
            "depth_percent": 0.0,
            "question": "What is the disease associated with the most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO?",
            "frequency": 1,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Clade I mpox",
            "needle": "The most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO is Clade I mpox.",
            "context_length": 5000,
            "depth_percent": 100.0,
            "question": "What is the disease associated with the most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO?",
            "frequency": 8,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Clade III, the most recent outbreak declared by WHO, is Clade III.",
            "needle": "The most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO is Clade I mpox.",
            "context_length": 5000,
            "depth_percent": 25.0,
            "question": "What is the disease associated with the most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO?",
            "frequency": 1,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Clade I mpox, the most recent outbreak declared by WHO, is a variant of the virus that causes mpox.",
            "needle": "The most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO is Clade I mpox.",
            "context_length": 5000,
            "depth_percent": 50.0,
            "question": "What is the disease associated with the most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO?",
            "frequency": 1,
            "hallucination_type": "Excess Incorrect Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Clade I mpox, the most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO, is a variant of the original SARS-CoV-2 virus.",
            "needle": "The most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO is Clade I mpox.",
            "context_length": 5000,
            "depth_percent": 75.0,
            "question": "What is the disease associated with the most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO?",
            "frequency": 1,
            "hallucination_type": "Excess Incorrect Retrieval"
        }
    ],
    "relevant": [
        {
            "model_response": "mpox",
            "needle": "The most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO is Clade I mpox.",
            "context_length": 0,
            "depth_percent": 0.0,
            "question": "What is the disease associated with the most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO?",
            "frequency": 5,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "mpox",
            "needle": "The most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO is Clade I mpox.",
            "context_length": 0,
            "depth_percent": 100.0,
            "question": "What is the disease associated with the most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO?",
            "frequency": 5,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "mpox",
            "needle": "The most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO is Clade I mpox.",
            "context_length": 0,
            "depth_percent": 25.0,
            "question": "What is the disease associated with the most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO?",
            "frequency": 5,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "mpox",
            "needle": "The most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO is Clade I mpox.",
            "context_length": 0,
            "depth_percent": 50.0,
            "question": "What is the disease associated with the most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO?",
            "frequency": 5,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "mpox",
            "needle": "The most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO is Clade I mpox.",
            "context_length": 0,
            "depth_percent": 75.0,
            "question": "What is the disease associated with the most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO?",
            "frequency": 5,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern (PHEIC) is the 2022 monkeypox outbreak.",
            "needle": "The most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO is Clade I mpox.",
            "context_length": 1250,
            "depth_percent": 0.0,
            "question": "What is the disease associated with the most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO?",
            "frequency": 2,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Clade I mpox",
            "needle": "The most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO is Clade I mpox.",
            "context_length": 1250,
            "depth_percent": 100.0,
            "question": "What is the disease associated with the most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO?",
            "frequency": 4,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern (PHEIC) is the 2022\u20132023 monkeypox outbreak.",
            "needle": "The most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO is Clade I mpox.",
            "context_length": 1250,
            "depth_percent": 25.0,
            "question": "What is the disease associated with the most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO?",
            "frequency": 1,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern (PHEIC) is the 2022\u20132023 mpox outbreak.",
            "needle": "The most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO is Clade I mpox.",
            "context_length": 1250,
            "depth_percent": 50.0,
            "question": "What is the disease associated with the most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO?",
            "frequency": 1,
            "hallucination_type": "Excess Incorrect Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern (PHEIC) is the 2022 monkeypox outbreak.",
            "needle": "The most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO is Clade I mpox.",
            "context_length": 1250,
            "depth_percent": 75.0,
            "question": "What is the disease associated with the most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO?",
            "frequency": 2,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Mpox",
            "needle": "The most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO is Clade I mpox.",
            "context_length": 2500,
            "depth_percent": 0.0,
            "question": "What is the disease associated with the most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO?",
            "frequency": 5,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Clade I mpox",
            "needle": "The most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO is Clade I mpox.",
            "context_length": 2500,
            "depth_percent": 100.0,
            "question": "What is the disease associated with the most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO?",
            "frequency": 4,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Mpox",
            "needle": "The most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO is Clade I mpox.",
            "context_length": 2500,
            "depth_percent": 25.0,
            "question": "What is the disease associated with the most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO?",
            "frequency": 5,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Mpox",
            "needle": "The most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO is Clade I mpox.",
            "context_length": 2500,
            "depth_percent": 50.0,
            "question": "What is the disease associated with the most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO?",
            "frequency": 5,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Ebola",
            "needle": "The most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO is Clade I mpox.",
            "context_length": 2500,
            "depth_percent": 75.0,
            "question": "What is the disease associated with the most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO?",
            "frequency": 1,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Mpox",
            "needle": "The most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO is Clade I mpox.",
            "context_length": 3750,
            "depth_percent": 0.0,
            "question": "What is the disease associated with the most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO?",
            "frequency": 5,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Clade I mpox",
            "needle": "The most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO is Clade I mpox.",
            "context_length": 3750,
            "depth_percent": 100.0,
            "question": "What is the disease associated with the most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO?",
            "frequency": 4,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Swine flu",
            "needle": "The most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO is Clade I mpox.",
            "context_length": 3750,
            "depth_percent": 25.0,
            "question": "What is the disease associated with the most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO?",
            "frequency": 1,
            "hallucination_type": "Irrelevant Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern (PHEIC) by the World Health Organization (WHO) is the 2022 monkeypox outbreak.",
            "needle": "The most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO is Clade I mpox.",
            "context_length": 3750,
            "depth_percent": 50.0,
            "question": "What is the disease associated with the most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO?",
            "frequency": 1,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Mpox",
            "needle": "The most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO is Clade I mpox.",
            "context_length": 3750,
            "depth_percent": 75.0,
            "question": "What is the disease associated with the most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO?",
            "frequency": 5,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO is the 2019-nCoV outbreak.",
            "needle": "The most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO is Clade I mpox.",
            "context_length": 5000,
            "depth_percent": 0.0,
            "question": "What is the disease associated with the most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO?",
            "frequency": 1,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Clade I mpox",
            "needle": "The most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO is Clade I mpox.",
            "context_length": 5000,
            "depth_percent": 100.0,
            "question": "What is the disease associated with the most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO?",
            "frequency": 4,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by the World Health Organization (WHO) is the 2019-nCoV outbreak.",
            "needle": "The most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO is Clade I mpox.",
            "context_length": 5000,
            "depth_percent": 25.0,
            "question": "What is the disease associated with the most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO?",
            "frequency": 1,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by the World Health Organization (WHO) is the 2019-nCoV outbreak, which was declared on January 30, 2",
            "needle": "The most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO is Clade I mpox.",
            "context_length": 5000,
            "depth_percent": 50.0,
            "question": "What is the disease associated with the most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO?",
            "frequency": 1,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by the World Health Organization (WHO) is the 2019 novel coronavirus (COVID-19) outbreak.",
            "needle": "The most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO is Clade I mpox.",
            "context_length": 5000,
            "depth_percent": 75.0,
            "question": "What is the disease associated with the most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO?",
            "frequency": 1,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        }
    ],
    "relevant_misleading": [
        {
            "model_response": "mpox",
            "needle": "The most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO is Clade I mpox.",
            "context_length": 0,
            "depth_percent": 0.0,
            "question": "What is the disease associated with the most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO?",
            "frequency": 7,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "mpox",
            "needle": "The most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO is Clade I mpox.",
            "context_length": 0,
            "depth_percent": 100.0,
            "question": "What is the disease associated with the most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO?",
            "frequency": 7,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "mpox",
            "needle": "The most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO is Clade I mpox.",
            "context_length": 0,
            "depth_percent": 25.0,
            "question": "What is the disease associated with the most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO?",
            "frequency": 7,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "mpox",
            "needle": "The most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO is Clade I mpox.",
            "context_length": 0,
            "depth_percent": 50.0,
            "question": "What is the disease associated with the most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO?",
            "frequency": 7,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "mpox",
            "needle": "The most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO is Clade I mpox.",
            "context_length": 0,
            "depth_percent": 75.0,
            "question": "What is the disease associated with the most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO?",
            "frequency": 7,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Mpox",
            "needle": "The most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO is Clade I mpox.",
            "context_length": 1250,
            "depth_percent": 0.0,
            "question": "What is the disease associated with the most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO?",
            "frequency": 1,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Clade I mpox",
            "needle": "The most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO is Clade I mpox.",
            "context_length": 1250,
            "depth_percent": 100.0,
            "question": "What is the disease associated with the most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO?",
            "frequency": 10,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "mpox",
            "needle": "The most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO is Clade I mpox.",
            "context_length": 1250,
            "depth_percent": 25.0,
            "question": "What is the disease associated with the most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO?",
            "frequency": 7,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "mpox",
            "needle": "The most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO is Clade I mpox.",
            "context_length": 1250,
            "depth_percent": 50.0,
            "question": "What is the disease associated with the most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO?",
            "frequency": 7,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Clade I mpox",
            "needle": "The most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO is Clade I mpox.",
            "context_length": 1250,
            "depth_percent": 75.0,
            "question": "What is the disease associated with the most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO?",
            "frequency": 10,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Clade I mpox",
            "needle": "The most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO is Clade I mpox.",
            "context_length": 2500,
            "depth_percent": 0.0,
            "question": "What is the disease associated with the most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO?",
            "frequency": 10,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Clade I mpox",
            "needle": "The most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO is Clade I mpox.",
            "context_length": 2500,
            "depth_percent": 100.0,
            "question": "What is the disease associated with the most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO?",
            "frequency": 10,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by the World Health Organization (WHO) is the 2019-nCoV outbreak, which began in Wuhan, China, in December",
            "needle": "The most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO is Clade I mpox.",
            "context_length": 2500,
            "depth_percent": 25.0,
            "question": "What is the disease associated with the most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO?",
            "frequency": 1,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Clade I mpox",
            "needle": "The most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO is Clade I mpox.",
            "context_length": 2500,
            "depth_percent": 50.0,
            "question": "What is the disease associated with the most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO?",
            "frequency": 10,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Clade I mpox",
            "needle": "The most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO is Clade I mpox.",
            "context_length": 2500,
            "depth_percent": 75.0,
            "question": "What is the disease associated with the most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO?",
            "frequency": 10,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Clade III mpox",
            "needle": "The most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO is Clade I mpox.",
            "context_length": 3750,
            "depth_percent": 0.0,
            "question": "What is the disease associated with the most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO?",
            "frequency": 1,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Clade I mpox",
            "needle": "The most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO is Clade I mpox.",
            "context_length": 3750,
            "depth_percent": 100.0,
            "question": "What is the disease associated with the most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO?",
            "frequency": 10,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by the World Health Organization (WHO) is the 2019-nCoV outbreak.",
            "needle": "The most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO is Clade I mpox.",
            "context_length": 3750,
            "depth_percent": 25.0,
            "question": "What is the disease associated with the most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO?",
            "frequency": 1,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Clade I mpox",
            "needle": "The most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO is Clade I mpox.",
            "context_length": 3750,
            "depth_percent": 50.0,
            "question": "What is the disease associated with the most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO?",
            "frequency": 10,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Clade I mpox",
            "needle": "The most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO is Clade I mpox.",
            "context_length": 3750,
            "depth_percent": 75.0,
            "question": "What is the disease associated with the most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO?",
            "frequency": 10,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Clade II mpox",
            "needle": "The most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO is Clade I mpox.",
            "context_length": 5000,
            "depth_percent": 0.0,
            "question": "What is the disease associated with the most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO?",
            "frequency": 4,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Clade I mpox",
            "needle": "The most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO is Clade I mpox.",
            "context_length": 5000,
            "depth_percent": 100.0,
            "question": "What is the disease associated with the most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO?",
            "frequency": 10,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Clade II mpox",
            "needle": "The most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO is Clade I mpox.",
            "context_length": 5000,
            "depth_percent": 25.0,
            "question": "What is the disease associated with the most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO?",
            "frequency": 4,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Clade II mpox",
            "needle": "The most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO is Clade I mpox.",
            "context_length": 5000,
            "depth_percent": 50.0,
            "question": "What is the disease associated with the most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO?",
            "frequency": 4,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Clade II mpox",
            "needle": "The most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO is Clade I mpox.",
            "context_length": 5000,
            "depth_percent": 75.0,
            "question": "What is the disease associated with the most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO?",
            "frequency": 4,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        }
    ]
}